Paul Muldoon papers, 1939-2010
Emory University
- Printed material, circa 1940s-2005, Series 4; Boxes 35-37, 90-98 and OP 12-148, 168-172
  - Writings by others, 1969-2005, Subseries 4.2; Boxes 35, 92 and OP 72-135
    - Times Literary Supplement, August 10, 1984, "The periodicals, 20: The Honest Ulsterman," article re: Honest Ulsterman with mention of Muldoon (Box OP90)
    - The Sunday Times, October 28, 1984, "High jinks at Wexford," review of opera with tenor Patrick Power's and producer Andy Hinds's names circled (Box OP91)
    - Times Literary Supplement, December 21, 1984, pp. 1473-76 (Box OP92)
    - Times Literary Supplement, January 25, 1985, pp.89-92 (Box OP93)
    - Announcement for Cambridge Poetry Festival: Fringe 85, enclosed with June 10, 1985 letter from Jean Hanff Korelitz (Box OP94)
    - Voice, April 21, 1987, announcement of Muldoon Academy of American Poets reading with Medbh McGuckian, with drawing and profile of Muldoon (Box OP95)
    - The Independent, May 14, 1987, "Just the boy for the verse stuff," article on Muldoon by Peter Forbes (Box OP96)
    - Irish Literary Supplement, Fall 1987, interview of Muldoon with Kevin Barry, full issue (Box OP97)
    - London Review of Books, May 5, 1988, "Anglo-Irish Occasions" by Seamus Heaney (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - Observer Magazine, September 25, 1988, "Well Versed" article with mention of Paul Muldoon by poet Hugo Williams (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - Times Literary Supplement, January 27-February 2, 1989, pp. 83-86 (Box OP98)
    - Times Literary Supplement, February 10-16, 1989, including review of Kearney book, Transitions: Narratives in modern Irish culture (Box OP99)
    - The Sunday Times, February 12, 1989, Screen section (Box OP100)
    - The Irishman, April/June 1989, "Muldoon Brings Poetry to Berkeley," article by Carol Vogl (Box OP101)
    - Times Literary Supplement, November 24-30, 1989, "Escape into the ineffable," article by Terry Eagleton with mention of Muldoon (Box OP102)
    - London Review of Books, January 25, 1990, "Davie's Rap" by Neil Corcoran (Box OP103)
    - Collegian: Massachusetts Daily, May 11, 1990, "Poet-prof stays modest: Irish Prof. Muldoon speaks on craft," article by Kerry Herlihy, three copies of full issue (Box OP104)
    - De Volkskrant, June 20, 1990, "Moeders skelet opdelven voor een gedicht," article on Muldoon with photograph (Box OP105)
    - The Irish Times, August 21, 1990, "Poets who work to keep things secret," article re: Yeats Summer School discussion by Carol; Coulter with discussion and photograph of Muldoon (Box OP106)
    - Harpers and Queens, November 1990, review of Madoc by Nick Everett (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - The New Republic, November 19, 1990, "What is World Poetry?" by Stephen Owen, photocopy (Box 35, Folder 30)
    - Literatorul, 1994, translation by Marin Sorescu of seven poems by Muldoon (Box OP107)
    - Times Literary Supplement, February 15, 1991, pp. 9-10 [clipped fora article on Auden?] (Box OP108)
    - Accent, February 28, 1991, "Paul Muldoon: A modern day Seanachie," article by Corinne Pavlis with "Why Brownlee Left" (Box OP109)
    - The New York Times, April 7, 1991, "Senior Thesis Debated: Enrichment or Torture?" article re: Princeton University found in file labeled "Students" (Box OP110)
    - City Tribune, April 12, 1991, photograph of Muldoon at International Poetry Festival, Cuirt, 1991 (Box OP111)
    - The Irish Times, April 12, 1991, pp. 1-2, 25-26 (Box OP112)
    - The New York Times, May 12, 1991, New Jersey Weekly section (Box OP113)
    - The Princeton Packet, May 14, 1991, announcement of "Authors' Party" with profile and photograph of Muldoon (Box OP114)
    - Sydsvenska Dagbladet, [May] 22, 1991, "I hogsta grad irlandsk," article on Muldoon with photograph and translation of "Raven," full issue (Box OP115)
    - Diversion, June 1991, "A Toast to Irish Writing," article by Ann Jones with mention of Muldoon (Box 35, Folder 31)
    - DN. Kultur and Nojen, June 4, 1991, "Nordirlandare fornyar engelska poesin," article by Ola Larsmo on Paul Muldoon with note for Larsmo attached (Box OP116)
    - Voice, July 30, 1991, "Coleridge and Southey's Bogus Journey," clipping and photocopy of review of Madoc by Geoffrey Stokes with copy of contents page (Box 35, Folder 32)
    - The New York Times, December 10, 1991, with article on Joesph Brodsky (Box OP117)
    - Pipe Dream, January 28, 1992, "Irish poets speak of life in a foreign land," article including section on Muldoon (Box OP118)
    - Gourmet, March 1992, letter to the editor mentioning Madison Opera Guild production of The Shining Brow (Box 35, Folder 33)
    - The New York Times, March 1992, letters to the editor re: exclusion of gay and lesbian persons from St. Patrick's Day parade (Box 35, Folder 34)
    - The Recorder, Summer 1992, review of Madoc: A Mystery by Robert; Tracy, photocopy of review and cover page (Box 35, Folder 35)
    - Times Literary Supplement, December 25, 1992, full issue (Box OP119)
    - The Irish Times, January 16, 1993, "A Weave of Words," review by Catherine Foley including Nuala Ní Dhomhnaill's The Astrakhan Cloak, translated by Muldoon, two photocopies (Box 35, Folder 36)
    - The Sunday Tribune, January 17, 1993, "Sly witches on a wild night," review by Connor Kelley including Nuala Ní Dhomhnaill's The Astrakhan Cloak, translated by Muldoon, two photocopies (Box 35, Folder 37)
    - [Financial Times?], February 7, 1993, "Through a glass, darkly," article re: politics in Northern Ireland with epigraph from Muldoon's "The Boundary Commission" (Box OP120)
    - Fortnight, April 1993, "Subconscious voyager," review by Frankie Sewell of Nuala Ní Dhomhnaill's The Astrakhan Cloak, translated by Muldoon, photocopy with paragraph highlighted (Box 35, Folder 38)
    - The Globe and Mail, Harbourfront Poetry Festival special section, April 10, 1993, "Let the readings begin" and "From six continents in only six days," announcement of readings with profile of Muldoon (Box OP121)
    - The New York Times, April 28, 1993, "Frank Lloyd Wright Joins Opera's Pantheon," review of The Shining Brow by James Oestreich, The Living Section and separate clip (Box OP122)
    - The New Yorker, May 17, 1993, "The Singing Architect" by Paul Griffiths, article on Muldoon and Hagen opera The Shining Brow, full issue (Box 35, Folder 39)
    - The Irish Voice, May 25, 1993, "Ireland's Next Nobel Prospect?" article on Muldoon by Patricia Jameson-Sammartano, 2 photocopies (Box 35, Folder 40)
    - Oxford Poetry, Summer 1993, "The Poetry of Architecture," review of The Shining Brow by Tim Kendall, 2pp., photocopy (Box 35, Folder 41)
    - Poetry Review, [June 1993?], "Hearsay" column by Kevan Johnson with mention of Muldoon and John Osborne's review of The New Poetry with mention of Muldoon (Box 35, Folder 42)
    - London Review of Books, August 19, 1993, with review of The Shining Brow by Paul Driver, full issue (Box OP123)
    - ILS, Fall 1993, "Going For It--And Succeeding," review by Briona Nic Dhiarmada of Nuala Ní Dhomhnaill's The Astrakhan Cloak, translated by Muldoon (Box OP124)
    - The New Republic, November 1, 1993, "Index of First Lines: from The Penguin Book of Contemporary Irish Poetry and Poets from the North of Ireland," poem by Annie Dillard, photocopy (Box 35, Folder 43)
    - North Dakota Quarterly, Winter 1993, "Another Side of Paul Muldoon," Paul Scott Stanfield (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Learning the Trade: Essays on W.B. Yeats and Contemporary Poetry, Locust Hill Press, 1993, annotated photocopy of chapter, "Questioning Yeats: Paul Muldoon's '7, Middagh Street,'" Jonathan Allison (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - A Small Nation's Contribution to the World, International Association for the Study of Anglo-Irish Literature, 1993, photocopied book chapter, "Mask Lyrics in the Poetry of Paul Muldoon and Derek Mahon," István D. Rács (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Times Literary Supplement, February 5, 1994, "To the goddess Anorexia," review by Elaine Showalter of Maud Ellman's book The Hunger Artists, photocopy (Box 35, Folder 44)
    - The New York Times, February 11, 1994, announcement of Pink Floyd concert with confirmation number written in Muldoon's hand (Box OP125)
    - Publisher's Weekly, August 29, 1994, review of The Annals of Chile (Box 35, Folder 45)
    - Times Literary Supplement, September 2, 1994, "Un-American Daughter," review of Sally Belfrage's book Un-American Activities by Jean Hanff Korelitz (Box 35, Folder 46)
    - U.S. 1 [?], October 26, 1994, "Literati: Poems, Etc. From Paul Muldoon," re: publication of Annals of Chile (Box OP126)
    - Times Literary Supplement, December 16, 1994, full issue (Box OP127)
    - Time Off, June 30, 1995, "Under the Proverbial Gun" (Box OP128)
    - Southern Review, Summer 1995, "Ciaran Carson's Parturiant Partition: the 'Crack' in MacNeice's 'More Than Glass,'" Guinn Batten (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Études Irlandaises, Autumn 1995, "'Everything Provisional': Fictive Possibility and the Poetry of Paul Muldoon and Ciaran Carson," Jonathan Allison (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Irish University Review, Autumn-Winter 1995, "'Parallel to the Parallel Realm': Paul Muldoon's Madoc--A Mystery," Tim Kendall (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - The Georgia Review, Winter 1995, book review, A Terrible Beauty: The Politics in Poetry, reviewed by Judith Kitchen (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - P.N. Review, November-December 1995, "Paul Muldoon and the Exploding Sestina," Fenella Copplestone (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - The Hollins Critic, February 1996, "Paul Muldoon: 'Time-Switch Taped to the Trough,'" Harriet Zinnes (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - Princeton University Bulletin, April 15, 1996, "Taking the Air with James McCosh, Prospect Gardens, February 1996" (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - Honest Ulsterman, Autumn 1996, interview with Muldoon, Stephen Magee (Box 92, Folder 11)
    - The Mai, November 10, 1996, "Dialogue on Drama, Marina Carr, Emily Mann and Paul Muldoon" (Box 92, Folder 12)
    - South Atlantic Quarterly, Winter 1996, "'He Could Barely Tell One from the Other': The Borderline Disorders of Paul Muldoon's Poetry," Guinn Batten (Box 92, Folder 13)
    - Bullán, 1996, "Utopia in the New World: Paul Muldoon's America," Carol Tell (Box 92, Folder 14)
    - A Celtic Florilegium: Studies in Memory of Brendan O Hehir, Celtic Studies Publications, 1996, "Sailing Strange Seas of Thought: Imrama, Máel Dúin to Muldoon," photocopy of book chapter by Robert Tracy (Box 92, Folder 15)
    - Poetry Ireland Review 54, 1996, "An Alarming Word," Carol Rubens (Box 92, Folder 16)
    - Études Irlandaises, Spring 1997, "An Interview with Paul Muldoon," Dominique Gauthier (Box 92, Folder 17)
    - Hudson Review, Spring 1997, "Irish Poetry at the Crossroads," David Mason (Box 92, Folder 18)
    - New Hibernia Review, Fall 1997, "A Land 'Not Borrowed but Purloined': Paul Muldoon's Indians," Jacqueline McCurry (Box 92, Folder 19)
    - Notes on Modern Irish Literature, 1997, "Crafty Inklings: Sonnets by Paul Muldoon," Jacqueline McCurry (Box 92, Folder 20)
    - Thumbscrew, Winter 1997/1998, "A Mixed Marriage: The Strange Affair of Sylvia Plath and Paul Muldoon," Ivan Phillips (Box 92, Folder 21)
    - The Sunday Times, October 4, 1998 (Box 92, Folder 22)
    - The Long Poem Group Newsletter, number 7, November 1998, "A Drink with Paul Muldoon," interview by Sebastian Barker (Box 92, Folder 23)
    - English Studies Leipzig, "Bibliography," printed from University of Leipzig website, December 1998 (Box 92, Folder 24)
    - Michigan Quarterly Review, Winter 1998, "The Invention of the I: A Conversation with Paul Muldoon," Earl G. Ingersoll (Box 92, Folder 25)
    - Irish Review 23, 1998, "Piece Talk," Guinn Batten (Box 92, Folder 26)
    - Magyar Naplo, 1998, translations of Muldoon's "Maggot" and "Train" into Hungarian by Határ Gyõzõ (Box 92, Folder 27)
    - The Reader, 1998, "Bouncing off the Walls: Muldoon, Paterson, Armitage and the Modern Sonnet," Jeremy Noel-Tod (Box 92, Folder 28)
    - Robert Frost Review, 1998, "'But all the fun's in how you say a thing': Robert Frost and Paul Muldoon," Jacqueline McCurry (Box 92, Folder 29)
    - London Magazine, February/March 1999, "In Performance," John O'Donoghue (Box 92, Folder 30)
    - London Review of Books, July 15, 1999, "Shoes Once Shod in a Blacksmith's Shop," "Figures in a Paddock," John Kinsella (Box 92, Folder 31)
    - The Sunday Times, June 9, 1999, "Cradle Song for Asher" (Box 92, Folder 32)
    - The Irish Times, December 31, 1999, "Right from the Heart," (Box 92, Folder 33)
    - English Studies Leipzig, "Paul Muldoon Pages," printed from University of Leipzig website, 1999 (Box 92, Folder 34)
    - Cartographic Perspectives, Spring 2000, "Poems Shaped like Maps: (Di)Versifying the Teaching of Geography, II," Adele Haft (Box 92, Folder 35)
    - Printed from website, www.ireland.com, "100 Favourite Irish Poems," June 3, 2000, unidentified author (Box 92, Folder 36)
    - Contemporary Literature, Summer 2000, "Skirmishes on the Border: The Evolution and Function of Paul Muldoon's Fuzzy Rhyme," Andrew Osborn (Box 92, Folder 37)
    - New Hibernia Review, Winter 2000, "'The Eye That Scanned It:' The Picture Poems of Heaney, Muldoon and McGuckian," Shane Murphy (Box 92, Folder 38)
    - Publishers Weekly, April 27, 2001, "Paul Muldoon, Head," Susan Wheeler (Box 92, Folder 39)
    - Printed from website, www.pgil-eirdata.org, circa 2001, "Paul Muldoon: Commentary," unidentified author (Box 92, Folder 40)
    - Printed from website, www.fact-index.com, 2003, entry about Paul Muldoon, unidentified author (Box 92, Folder 41)
    - Advance on the Web, January 26, 2004, "Poetry Makes Sense of Key Moments in Life," Skye Dent (Box 92, Folder 42)
    - Lily. A Monthly Online Literary Review, January 2004, interview with Muldoon (Box 92, Folder 43)
    - Irish University Review, August 2004, "The Legacy of Yeats in Contemporary Irish Literature," Ronald Schuchard (Box 92, Folder 44)
    - Modern Haiku, Summer 2004, "A Poet's Haiku: Paul Muldoon," William J. Higginson (Box 92, Folder 45)
    - The Aspen Times, January 14, 2005, "Paul Muldoon--At Arms Length," Eben Harrell (Box 92, Folder 46)
    - Undated or unidentified
    - [Independent], no date, Tom Paulin on Poetry recommending Nuala Ní Dhomhnaill's Pharoh's Daughters, with some translations by Muldoon, and The Shining Brow by Muldoon (Box OP129)
    - Unidentified source, "An Irish poet not going gentle into that good night," photocopy of article on Patrick Kavanagh by Peter Dunn [perhaps attached to November 27, 1989 letter to Muldoon from Gerard Quinn?] (Box OP130)
    - Unidentified source, "Dichters zijn goudzoekers die worden opgepakt," article on Poetry International with mention of Muldoon (Box OP131)
    - Unidentified source, "Poetry eregeld voor gevangen Song Lin," article on Poetry International with mention and photograph of Muldoon (Box OP132)
    - Unidentified source, letter from Muldoon in Gaelic announcing first BBC Irish Language Broadcasts on Radio Ulster (Box OP133)
    - Unidentified source, "A Little More of the Sense of Ireland," with section on Muldoon (Box OP134)
    - Unidentified source, "The Heaney Phenomenon" by Desmond Fennell, photocopy of article (Box OP135)
    - Who's Who in New Jersey, draft of Muldoon's entry, photocopy (Box 35, Folder 47)
    - Unidentified magazine source, announcement of Muldoon reading with photograph and profile (Box 35, Folder 48)
    - Verse, Vol. 11, No. 1 no date, "Paul Muldoon and the Art of Allusion," photocopy of article by Tim Kendall (Box 35, Folder 49)
    - Unidentified source, two photocopied maps labeled "Escape and Resistance, July-December 1943," and "Jews Massacred Between 17 July and 31 August 1941," with minimal holograph notes (Box 35, Folder 50)
    - Unidentified source, "Primal Forms and Primal Divisions," photocopy of article by Erik Saxon (Box 35, Folder 51)
    - Noonday, no date, announcement of The Annals of Chile with selected quotations from reviews (Box 35, Folder 52)
    - Unidentified source, critical excerpts on Muldoon including Geoffrey Stokes, Andrew Motion, and John Mole, 2 pp. photocopy (Box 35, Folder 53)
    - Unidentified magazine source, "The Poet" profiles of Muldoon and Nuala Ní Dhomhnaill, 2 copies (Box 35, Folder 54)
    - Unidentified newspaper source [New York Times?], "A Changing Country," article re: social issues in Ireland (Box 35, Folder 55)
    - Unidentified newspaper source, "Poet Paul Muldoon to Read at Arts Council," article announcing Muldoon reading (Box 35, Folder 56)
    - Unidentified source, "Perish the thought," short article re: Arts Council invite to Muldoon, photocopy (Box 35, Folder 57)
    - Unidentified newspaper source, "Irish poet reads from work," article on Muldoon reading by Ed Nest (Box 35, Folder 58)
    - Unidentified newspaper source, "Literati," with announcement of Muldoon reading (Box 35, Folder 59)
    - Unidentified newspaper source, "3 from area win Guggenheims," with section on Muldoon (Box 35, Folder 60)
    - Unidentified source, "Sulking politico questions Nobel Prize," article by Clarence Brown re: Toni Morrison's Nobel Prize with mention of Muldoon (Box 35, Folder 61)
    - Contemporary Poets entry on Muldoon, photocopy (Box 35, Folder 62)
    - Unidentified source, September 25 (no year), BBC TV and radio listings (Box 35, Folder 63)
    - Unidentified source, "Poetry on the Loose," article by James Simmons (Box 35, Folder 64)
    - Unidentified source, "Baring; Mother Ireland's Soul," article by Ann O'Byrne re: Seamus Heaney, Nuala Ní Dhomhnaill, Liam de Paor, Paul Muldoon, William Trevor, and Derek Mahon, with photographs of each (Box 35, Folder 65)
    - Unidentified source, [1987?], "Like a Wedding Through the Moy," with discussion of Muldoon, photocopy of article (Box 35, Folder 66)
    - Unidentified source, literary/biographical entry on Muldoon, photocopy (Box 35, Folder 67)
    - Unidentified source, "Freelance" by Hugo William[?], with mention of Muldoon (Box 35, Folder 68)
    - Unidentified source, "Opera houses," review of Muldoon's The Shining Brow by Peter Sirr (Box 35, Folder 69)
    - Unidentified source, "The State of Poetry," with section devoted to Muldoon (Box 35, Folder 70)
    - Miscellaneous printed material (Box 35, Folder 71)
    - Barnes and Noble, printed from company website, no date, author page for Paul Muldoon, unidentified author (Box 92, Folder 47)
    - "Paul Muldoon: The Annals of Chile," Shane Murphy, no date (Box 92, Folder 48)
    - Ploughshares, "About Paul Muldoon," Sven Birkerts, no date (Box 92, Folder 49)
    - Printed from website, www.contemporarywriters.com, no date, entry on Paul Muldoon for Booktrust, Peter Forbes (Box 92, Folder 50)
    - Printed from website, www.litencyc.com, no date, entry on Paul Muldoon, by Ivan Phillips (Box 92, Folder 51)
    - Unidentified journal, no date, "Only Connect," Jeremy Noel-Tod (Box 92, Folder 52)
    - Critical Survey of Poetry, no date,entry on Paul Muldoon, George O'Brien (Box 92, Folder 53)
    - "The Sunday Poem," no date, Ruth Padel [about "Quoof" by Paul Muldoon] (Box 92, Folder 54)
  - Clippings arranged by volume, 1973-2005, Subseries 4.3; Box 35, 93-95 and OP 136-148
    The subseries consists of clippings from newspapers and journals from 1973-2005, including reviews of Muldoon's works and interviews with Muldoon. Following Muldoon's arrangement, these clippings are arranged according to the volume they concern. There are additional folders containing material on commissioned works, such as the Oscar Wilde memorial, and material on Muldoon's collaborations with Warren Zevon. A large amount of unorganized and miscellaneous clippings follow.
    Arranged in chronological order by date of publication.
    - Poetry Introduction 2 (Box OP136)
    - New Weather (1973) (Box OP137)
    - Mules (1977) (Box OP13)
    - Why Brownlee Left (1980) (Box OP139)
    - Quoof (1983) (Box OP140)
    - Selected Poems 1968-1983 (1986) (Box OP141)
    - The Faber Book of Contemporary Irish Poetry, (1986) (Box OP144)
    - Meeting the British (1987) (Box OP142)
    - Madoc: A Mystery (1990) (Box OP145)
    - Madoc: A Mystery (United States, 1990) (Box OP146)
    - Selected Poems 1968-1986 (United States, 1993) (Box OP143)
    - The Annals of Chile (1994) (Box OP147)
    - Shining Brow, 1993-1997 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Paul Muldoon, by Tim Kendall, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - New Selected Poems, 1996-1998 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Oscar Wilde memorial, 1997-2000 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Princeton Stadium, 1998-1999 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Oxford Professorship of Poetry, 1999-2004 (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous science articles, various authors, 1998-1999 (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - To Ireland, I, 2000-2002 (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Poems 1968-1998, 2002-2003 (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - Zevon, Warren, 2002-2004 (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - Interviews/Articles (Box OP148)
    - Miscellaneous clippings from Muldoon (Box 35, Folder 71)
    - Miscellaneous clippings, 1993-1996 (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous clippings, 1997 (Box 93, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous clippings, 1998 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous clippings, 1999 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous clippings, 2000-2001 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous clippings, 2002 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous clippings, 2003 January-August (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous clippings, 2003 September-December (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous clippings, 2004 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous clippings, 2005 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous clippings, no date (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Printed/bound material, circa 1940s-2004, Subseries 4.4; Boxes 36-37, 96-98 and OP 171-172
    The subseries contains printed and bound material from the 1940s-2004, including full issues of selected journals and publications containing writings by or about Paul Muldoon or related authors.
    - Across the Roaring Hill, An Impression of Ulster Compiled from the Work of the Province's Writers, by David Grant, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - American Poet, Summer 1996 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - The American Scholar, Spring 1998 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - "Americans for the Arts, 2003 Annual Report," 2003 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Anseo, Spring 1995 (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - An tUltach, Imleabhar 46, Uimhir 4: Aibreán 1969 Antæus 58, Spring 1987 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Aquarius, No. 4, 1971 ("Irish Number") (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Avocado, February 2002 (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - "Beckett 90," festival program, with essays on Beckett by various authors, 1996 (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - "The Beckett Festival," program, with essays on Beckett by various authors, September 1999 (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Bishop's, Spring 2004, with article about lecture by Muldoon, delivered at the Bishop's School (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - Bomb, Fall 1998, with article on Muldoon and Yusef Komunyakaa (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - Bonded Shores, November 1997 (Box 96, Folder 10)
    - Bookforum, Winter 1998, with review of Paul Muldoon's Hay (Box OP171)
    - Boston College Magazine, Fall 2003 (Box 96, Folder 11)
    - Bulletin, American Acadmey of Arts and Sciences, winter 2001 (Box 96, Folder 12)
    - Cantonirico, Sergio Badilla (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - China, May 2004, featuring translations of poetry by Paul Muldoon and Nuala Ní Dhomhnaill into Chinese (Box 96, Folder 13)
    - College Green, Autumn 1995 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Concerning Poetry, Vol. 14, No. 2: "Concerning Irish Poetry Since W.B. Yeats" (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Contemporary Writers: Paul Muldoon, British Council, 1988 (Box 96, Folder 14)
    - Critical Inquiry, "Artists on Art: Now and in England," Vol. 3, No. 3, Spring 1977, by Seamus Heaney (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - De Levande Orden: Arets Antologi, March 21-26, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - El Muelle, Dimitris Kalokyris, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 9)